There's a wave of AI OFM reels going
viral right now, and almost all of them
are made with Seedance. So, I built a
system in Claude that takes any reel
that's already going viral and rebuilds
it with your own model in less than 10
minutes. I'm giving you the whole thing,
every Claude skill, every prompt,
complete for free in this video. All I
ask in return is that you drop a like
and write a nice comment what video I
should do next to help you make more
money. No gatekeeping. Both skills, all
the prompts, everything you saw today is
for free in my Discord. And if this
helps you, just drop a like and comment
what I should break down next.